Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series IX is arranged in 34 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. BYLAWS - DISTRICT COUNCILS
  - Sub-Series 206-1. Bylaws
    - Cleveland District Council, 1920-1942 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 206-2. Bylaws
    - Chicago Council of Chicago and Northwestern Lodges, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 206-3. Bylaws
    - Buffalo District Council, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 206-3. Bylaws
    - Niagara Frontier Council, 1920-1921 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 206-4. Bylaws
    - Columbus District Council, 1921-1928 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 206-5. Bylaws
    - Memphis District Council, 1921-1953 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 206-6. Bylaws
    - The Cincinnati District Council, 1921-1941 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 206-7. Bylaws
    - Twin City Council-St. Paul and Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 206-8. Bylaws
    - Iron Ore District Federation, 1921-1923 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 206-9. Bylaws
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Federation, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 206-10. Bylaws
    - Fort Worth District Council, 1922-1947 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 206-12. Bylaws
    - Philadelphia and Camden District, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 206-13. Bylaws
    - St. Louis District Council, 1922-1935 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 206-15. Bylaws
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 206-16. Bylaws
    - New Orleans District Council, 1923-1953 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 206-17. Bylaws
    - Mutual Benefit Association (Lodge No. 2168), 1923 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 206-18. Bylaws
    - Sick Relief Association of Lodge No. 768, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 206-19. Bylaws
    - Minneapolis Joint Council, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 206-20. Bylaws
    - Seattle Division Protective Committee-Northern Pacific Railway, 1924-1932 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 206-22. Bylaws
    - Relief Association. Lodge No. 85-Rules and Regulations (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 206-23. Bylaws
    - Toledo District Council, 1925-1931 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 206-25. Bylaws
    - Dallas District Council, 1926 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 206-26. Bylaws
    - New York District Committee, 1928-1937 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 206-27. Bylaws
    - Indianapolis District Council, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 206-28. Bylaws
    - Louisville District Council, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 206-29. Bylaws
    - New England District Council, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 206-30. Bylaws
    - Boston District Council, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 206-32. Bylaws
    - Toronto District Council, 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 206-33. Bylaws
    - Philadelphia District Council, 1938-1946 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 206-34. Bylaws
    - Jacksonville District Council, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 206-35. Bylaws
    - Baltimore District Council, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 206-36. Bylaws
    - Houston District Council, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 206-37. Bylaws
    - Joint Council of Lodges of the St. Louis. East St. Louis Area (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 206-38. Bylaws
    - Joint Council of Lodges of Kansas City and Springfield, Missouri, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 34)